kidsworldfun.com 2018-07-25

# Kids World Fun - Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how Kids World Fun uses and protects any information that you give Kids World Fun when you use this website. 

Kids World Fun is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. 

Kids World Fun may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 1st January 2014.   
**  
What we do with the information we gather**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons: 

» Internal record keeping.   
» We may use the information to improve our products and services.   
» We may periodically send latest updates which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.   
» From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests. 

**Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. 

**Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. 

**Contact Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the online form.
